What class and year are you?
I'm a first year, in Class 1. My name is Ninako Kinoshita.
Ren rejected another girl.
Some of those girls were notoriously cute, too.
If someone goes out of their way for me,
of course I'd appreciate the favor.
Weirdo.
If you don't confess first, someone else will take her.
Do you have a crush on Ichinose?
Even if Ren has a girlfriend,
my feelings for him won't just disappear.
I didn't fall for him, hoping anything would come out of this.
I just want him to know how happy I am to be in love.
Ren!
What's up?
Ren.
I...
I like you.
Thank you.
But I'm sorry. I already have a girlfriend.
Yeah. I know.
- Huh?
- I just wanted you to know how I felt.
Will you continue to be my friend regardless?
Sure.
Can you really be friends with someone who rejected you?
I can, easy. Piece of cake.
You think so?
I think it'll be pretty tough.
Not speaking to Ren would be worse.
You truly love him from the bottom of your heart, don't you?
Then I guess I'll take Daiki for myself.
Huh?
Actually, I already confessed to him.
- What?
- I'm still waiting for a response, though.
Since when did you have a crush on Daiki?
I'm not too sure myself.
I always admired how honest and devoted he was to you.
Before I knew it, I realized I liked him.
Does that mean... you hate me?
Of course not!
- Sayu...
- Ninako...
- Sayu!
- Ninako!
Good night, Mii.
Even if the person I like has someone they love already,
I can't deny the love I have for him.
That's all there is to this crush of mine.
[Hikarigasaki High School]
[Episode 2]
What should I say when I see Ren?
Morning, Ninako.
Morning.
Great job acting normal.
M-Morning.
Maybe I have a chance?
"Morning!"
"Morning."
"Morning?"
- "Morning..."
- Morning, Ichinose.
Morning.
- Morning!
- Morning.
Who are you again?
Sorry, wrong person.
Go right on ahead.
You're the girl who was rejected by Ren Ichinose.
How did you...
That's her, the one Ren rejected.
She apparently confessed right before summer break.
He shot her straight down.
That's what you get for confessing right at the station.
I want to disappear.
So that's what you meant by "wrong person".
Trying to "coincidentally" catch him in the morning? Cute.
Leaving already?
Ando.
What's so great about a blunt guy like him? I don't get it.
Huh?
What's up with Ninako?
Everyone was staring daggers into her at morning assembly.
Poor girl.
Alright everybody, settle down.
I've got an announcement to make.
The beautification committee will be having a meeting today.
[Yr 1, Class 1 Teacher: Toshio Hasebe]
Kinoshita.
Yes?
You weren't in any clubs or committees, right?
It's Ren. I have to say something.
Yo!
Yo.
Why are you here?
You weren't a part of the beautification committee
during our first term.
Our committee rep transferred schools over the summer.
I was forced into the role by Mr. Hasebe.
That's unlucky.
Right? So unlucky.
Phew! I'm acting normal.
You must feel so relieved.
Were you able to give him a proper greeting this time?
Don't mention that.
Ren hasn't heard a word of it. Not yet, at least.
You know her, Ando?
- Sure. Could I take the spot next to you?
- Go ahead.
Take this seat. It's another perfectly open spot.
Pushy, aren't you?
Hey.
So you're friends with Ren?
Not exactly. We just attended the same middle school.
I see.
Still crushing on Ren?
No.
Then give me your Line ID.
[T/N: A messaging/social media app]
I don't do social media.
Aw, man. Guess I'll just have to tell Ren
about your passionate stare from this morning.
[Ninako Kinoshita]
Score.
That guy acts like nothing happened,
even though he shot you down.
He doesn't get how hurt you are. What an insensitive dude.
He's not insensitive.
He's acting like nothing happened
so things don't get awkward for me.
That's just the sort of guy he is.
I know how awkward it can be
for the one who did the rejecting, too.
The only reason we're able to talk at all,
is because of Ren's thoughtfulness.
What're you staring at?
A gathering of girls you rejected.
- We're bringing her over.
- Great.
I see.
It's Ninako.
You said you needed me?
We figured you must be pissed off by Ren, too.
Did you hear? He's apparently dating a model.
Seriously?
Yeah, some girl saw them on a date over summer break.
What, so he's just a sucker for pretty faces? Yikes.
Wow, they're absolutely ruthless.
He has a girlfriend, and is a ladies man? Ugh, nasty.
I bet he totally looks down on us.
- Yeah.
- Definitely.
- He's so awful.
- He's only got his face going for him.
Ren isn't like that at all.
What were you all expecting from him?
What did you like about him?
You don't know anything about Ren.
Look at you, acting like a goody-two-shoes.
You think you're better than us?
This is so stupid.
You talk smack behind his back? That's just so, so, so stupid.
What a killjoy.
Let's just go.
What an interesting girl.
I'm not in the wrong. I know I'm not.
Ren's a nice guy.
I've experienced his kindness firsthand.
- You think that's his girlfriend?
- Woah!
Let's ask him about it.
What?
Hey, Ando!
Ren.
Ando.
And Kinoshita?
Is this your girlfriend?
Yeah.
My name is Mayuka Korenaga.
The name's Ando.
I'm Ninako Kinoshita.
Since we're all here, how about we go grab a bite together?
You're not ordering any food, Mayuka?
I have to watch my weight.
Meanwhile Ninako's munching away without a care in the world.
I think girls who eat heartily are adorable.
If it wasn't for my job, I'd be eating the same amount.
Speaking of, what do you see in a blunt guy like him anyway?
Ren only looks blunt and cold. He's really kind at heart.
Stop it, you're embarrassing me.
Aw, no need to get so shy.
Let's run for it!
Ninako, wait. I need to re-tie my shoes.
Hurry up, we'll miss our chance...
Wait, you're wearing loafers.
Busted, huh?
Alright, let's ditch them.
Huh?
Ando?
Ando, pause!
Why did we just leave?
I couldn't stand there and do nothing
when you looked so conflicted.
If this one doesn't work out, move on.
What's the point of a love that hurts? I don't get it.
You'll get it one day, Ando.
When you have a crush like mine, it'll become obvious.
Someone's acting all high-and-mighty.
I'll give you a half thank you.
You're right.
I was having a hard time watching those two.
But that's still no excuse for ditching them without a word.
That's why you get half of my gratitude.
Thanks for getting me out of there.
Morning, Ren.
I want to ask about yesteday.
Yeah, yeah. Our bad for ditching you guys.
But didn't you two have more fun alone? I sure did.
Don't get Kinoshita involved in your flings.
What do you mean?
She's not like those other girls you've messed around with.
Dude.
Are you Ninako's anything?
You have no right butting into her relationships with people.
Takumi, wanna come hang at my place today? No one's home.
Sorry, not happening.
We're ending things here, okay?
Toodles.
Sure.
- That was -
- Besides, you're the one who's messing around.
Acting like nothing's happened between you and Ninako?
News flash big guy, but no one calls that "being kind".
See you in class.
Don't go acting coy towards the guy who rejected you.
Ninako, did those two bump into you on purpose?
No.
I was just a bit careless.
- See you in class.
- Hey wait, Ninako!
Is everything okay?
No, it's just, Ninako...
I mean...
Well...
Are you trying to be considerate of me?
Don't bother.
I fell for you because of your devotion to Ninako.
I know there's nothing I can do about it.
You don't mind?
Doesn't it bother you that I keep crushing on Ninako?
What are you trying to say?
Be clear with me, or I won't get it.
You're not being fair to me right now.
Ren.
I'm sorry we ran off like that yesterday.
It really was a thoughtless move to pull.
Ando.
The committee leader sent me over to help.
Welcome, come join us.
Could you bundle these stacks for us?
Sure.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Ren.
- I...
- We're out of trash bags.
I'll go grab us some more.
What is he, a man who only knows extremes?
He hates me now.
No, he's just being stupid...
Hey, woah there.
What the - what was that?
Sorry.
Ninako?
Sorry, I won't do that ever again.
Ninako, where are you?
Don't hide from me.
I think he's gone now.
Thanks.
Ren?
[Next Episode]
Right this way.
Take it slow, and no need to panic.
You're such a weirdo, Kinoshita.
I like the way we are now.
I'm fine with keeping these feelings to myself.
You can't expect anything from Ren
so long as he has a girlfriend.
Use me.
I'll help you forget Ren, for good.
[Epilogue]
"We figured you must be pissed off, too"?
Don't group me with the rest of you.
Ninako.
I saw you being pestered by a gang of girls earlier.
You were watching?
Ren's put you in a real pickle, huh?
It's not Ren's fault.
What now?
How can you stand up for a guy who rejected you?
Well...
Hey, could you let her go already?
Sayu...
I will, if you trade me your Line ID.
Sure, I don't mind.
What?
You shouldn't give your ID away to just anyone.
- Why not?
- Seems dangerous.
I can make that judgement myself.
- You're not even friends with this dude.
- Would you look at that?
They act like a couple already.
Now, now. There's plenty of me to go around, you two.
- We're not fighting over you.
Right, sorry.
See? Don't trade IDs with such a player.
- I hope they find happiness together one day.
- We're practically classmates.
You barely know the dude.
Don't give your ID out to guys you don't know.
If you're so bothered, then you text me every day.